[
    {
        "question": "The Foster Business Library is located in which part of the UW campus?",
        "options": ["North", "West", "South", "Central"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "area",
        "correctAnswer": "North" 
    },
    {
        "question": "The Odegaard Undergradute Library offers what unique feature to students?",
        "options": ["24/7 Access", "Free Coffee", "Private Study Rooms", "Gym Facilities"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "environment",
        "correctAnswer": "24/7 Access" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Which library is directly adjacent to Red Square?",
        "options": ["Odegaard Undergraduate Library", "Foster Business Library", "Suzallo Library", "Health Sciences Library"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name":"name",
        "correctAnswer": "Odegaard Undergraduate Library"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which study spot is quiet and located in the North Campus with tables available?", 
        "options": ["Mary Gates Hall", "Denny Hall", "Foster Business Library", "IMA"], 
        "optionsType": "radio", 
        "name": "card",
        "correctAnswer": "Denny Hall"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which library has a cafe inside it?", 
        "options": ["Odegaard Undergraduate Library", "Foster Business Library", "Suzzallo Library", "Health Sciences Library?"], 
        "optionsType": "radio", 
        "name": "food",
        "correctAnswer": "Suzzallo Library"
    },
    {

        "question": "Which study spot is best known for its quiet reading room that resembles the halls of Hogwarts?",
        "options": ["Mary Gates Hall", "Odegaard Undergraduate Library", "Suzzallo Library", "The HUB"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "reading_room",
        "correctAnswer": "Suzzallo Library"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which study spot is found in the West Campus and features 'Modern' architecture and 'Whiteboards'?",
        "options": ["Maple Hall", "Odegaard Undergraduate Library", "Suzzallo Library", "Mary Gates Hall"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "whiteboards",
        "correctAnswer": "Denny Hall"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following study spots is NOT located in Central Campus?",
        "options": ["Foster Business Library", "Odegaard Undergraduate Library", "The HUB", "Engineering Building"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "Not_Central",
        "correctAnswer": "Foster Business Library"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which North Campus study spot features 'Quiet' ambiance and 'Tables'?",
        "options": ["Foster Business Library", "Mary Gates Hall", "The HUB", "IMA"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "Quiet_Tables",
        "correctAnswer": "Denny Hall"
    },
     {   "question": "Which study spot offers 'Whiteboards' but is not 'Popular'?",
        "options": ["The HUB", "Odegaard Undergraduate Library", "The HUB", "Engineering Building"],
        "optionsType": "radio",
        "name": "Not-Popular",
        "correctAnswer": "Engineering Building"
    }
]
